const arr = [{"id":0,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"A 3-year-old child with spastic diplegic cerebral palsy has spastic bilateral hamstrings. Which one of the following is the most likely cause?","answers":[{"option":"Jump gait","bool":true},{"option":"Hemiplegic gait","bool":false},{"option":"Crouch gait","bool":false},{"option":"W-sitting","bool":false},{"option":"Toe walk","bool":false}]},{"id":1,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"A 45-year-old male presents to the clinic with a complaint of lower back pain for 3 months. The pain is radiating to the right leg with numbness up to his foot. Pain is continuous, and bowel and bladder functions are intact. He has a history of hypertension for the past 14 years. On examination, the right straight leg raise test is 60 degrees, and the left is 90 degrees. Sciatic nerve stretch is negative, right piriformis test is positive, and Faber test is negative. Reflexes and myotomes are intact with dermatomes, and the heel and toe walk test are normal. Which of the following is the most likely diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"L5-S1 radiculopathy","bool":false},{"option":"Piriformis syndrome","bool":true},{"option":"Cauda equina syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"L4-L5 radiculopathy","bool":false},{"option":"Sciatica","bool":false}]},{"id":2,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"A 10-month-old baby was brought to the rehabilitation center by her parents, where the diagnosis of Erb's palsy was made. A rehabilitation physician would consider which type of orthoses for this patient, besides physiotherapy?","answers":[{"option":"Pancake splint","bool":false},{"option":"Slings-figure of 8 orthosis","bool":false},{"option":"Air-plane splint","bool":true},{"option":"Balanced forearm orthosis","bool":false},{"option":"A long arm cast","bool":false}]},{"id":3,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"A 50-year-old female presents in the clinic with grouped vesicular lesions over an erythematous base. The lesions have a dermatomal distribution associated with severe burning pain. Her past medical history is significant for diabetes mellitus for 10 years. Which of the following is the most likely diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Urticaria","bool":false},{"option":"Eczema","bool":false},{"option":"Herpes zoster","bool":true},{"option":"Impetigo","bool":false},{"option":"Herpes simplex","bool":false}]},{"id":4,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"A 55-year-old male patient came to the physician's clinic with complaint of left-sided weakness for the last month. For preventing subluxation of the shoulder in a hemiplegic patient, which of the following will the doctor prescribe?","answers":[{"option":"Balanced forearm orthosis","bool":false},{"option":"Taylor's brace","bool":false},{"option":"Figure-of-eight sling","bool":true},{"option":"Abductor splint","bool":false},{"option":"Air-plane splint","bool":false}]},{"id":5,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"A 24-year-old lady comes to a salon for her facial treatment. She has naturally beautiful red hair. This is probably because of the pigment pheomelanin produced by melanocytes. These pigment cells are the derivatives of which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Neural crest cells","bool":true},{"option":"Neuroectoderm","bool":false},{"option":"Endoderm","bool":false},{"option":"Ectoderm","bool":false},{"option":"Mesoderm","bool":false}]},{"id":6,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"A 25-year-old man lost his left foot in a road traffic accident. His level of amputation is ankle disarticulation, which is also known as which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Syme amputation","bool":true},{"option":"Lisfranc amputation","bool":false},{"option":"Partial Foot amputation","bool":false},{"option":"Chopart amputation","bool":false},{"option":"Ray resections","bool":false}]},{"id":7,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"A 3-year-old child was brought to the emergency department with recurrent episodes of pneumonia. On examination, it was observed that besides signs and symptoms of pneumonia there was also the presence of hypotonia, epicanthic folds, flat nasal bridge, small ears, and mouth. What is the most likely diagnosis of this case?","answers":[{"option":"Patau syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Turner syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Down syndrome","bool":true},{"option":"Kleinfelter syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Edward's syndrome","bool":false}]},{"id":8,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"A 45-year-old man with transtibial amputation came to amputee clinic for a functional prosthesis. Which of these is the most commonly prescribed foot?","answers":[{"option":"Impulse foot","bool":false},{"option":"Dynamic foot","bool":false},{"option":"Stationary ankle flexible (SARE)","bool":false},{"option":"Solid ankle cushion heel (SACH)","bool":true},{"option":"Multiaxial foot","bool":false}]},{"id":9,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"A 5-year-old boy presented with the complaint of bending of his trunk as noticed by his parents for 2 years. On radiological evaluation, a thoracolumbar curve was found out to be 11 degrees. Which of the following is the most appropriate management option for this patient?","answers":[{"option":"Orthotic intervention of curve progress to > 1 degree during interval follow up","bool":false},{"option":"Clinical and radiographic followup every 1-2 years till skeletal maturity","bool":false},{"option":"Observation for curves upto 40 degrees","bool":false},{"option":"Plan surgery if curve progress to > 20 degrees before skeletal maturity","bool":false},{"option":"Observation for curves upto 20 degrees","bool":true}]},{"id":10,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"A 5-year-old boy presented with generalized itching all over the body. On examination, there were excoriated papules over genitals, fingers, and toe web. Which of these is the most likely diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Psoriasis","bool":false},{"option":"Impetigo","bool":false},{"option":"Scabies","bool":true},{"option":"Chicken pox","bool":false},{"option":"Lichen planus","bool":false}]},{"id":11,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"A 70-year-old male with diabetes presents with recent right below-knee amputation secondary to infection in the foot. Which of these most important muscles should be strengthened to prepare for prosthetic ambulation?","answers":[{"option":"Hip extensor, knee extensor and hip abductors","bool":true},{"option":"Hip extensor, hip flexors, knee flexor","bool":false},{"option":"Hip abductors and adductors and knee flexors","bool":false},{"option":"Hip flexors, knee extensors knee flexor","bool":false},{"option":"Hip flexors, hip extensor and hip adductors","bool":false}]},{"id":12,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"A middle-aged female presents with acne, obesity, hirsutism, irregular menses. Which investigation will help in the diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Skin biopsy","bool":false},{"option":"Ultrasound of ovaries","bool":true},{"option":"ECG","bool":false},{"option":"Mammography","bool":false},{"option":"X-ray chest","bool":false}]},{"id":13,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"A middle-aged diabetic female has had a thickly crusted ulcer on her leg for the last 1 week. The crust is removed with difficulty. She describes that initially, there were small bullae with necrotic dry adherent crust and underlying ulceration which slowly with scarring. There is no history of travel. Which is the most likely diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Bullous impetigo","bool":false},{"option":"Bacterial folliculitis","bool":false},{"option":"Ecthyma","bool":true},{"option":"Infected eczema","bool":false},{"option":"Erysipelas","bool":false}]},{"id":14,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"A patient presenting with flexion contracture of the metacarpophalangeal (MCP), hyperextension of the proximal interphalangeal (PIP) joint, and the flexion of the distal interphalangeal (DIP) joint is seen in which of the following diseases?","answers":[{"option":"Osteoarthritis","bool":false},{"option":"Rheumatoid arthritis","bool":true},{"option":"Gout","bool":false},{"option":"Psoriatic arthritis","bool":false},{"option":"Systemic sclerosis","bool":false}]},{"id":15,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"A pregnant female come to her gynecologist and told her about the history of hemophilia in her family. She asked the doctor about the chance of presence of this disease in her child. The doctor calculated the risk and told her that it will be which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Female with 100% diseased","bool":false},{"option":"Female with 50% of carrier","bool":true},{"option":"Male with 1% diseased","bool":false},{"option":"Male or female with 50% diseased","bool":false},{"option":"Male with no disease","bool":false}]},{"id":16,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Acantholysis is defined as which of these?","answers":[{"option":"Loss of intercellular cohesion between dermal cells","bool":false},{"option":"Loss of intercellular cohesion between keratinocytes","bool":true},{"option":"Thickening and separation of stratum corneum","bool":false},{"option":"Infiltration of epidermis by inflammatory cells","bool":false},{"option":"Discontinuity of skin","bool":false}]},{"id":17,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Aminoacyl RNA synthases are required in which of these processes?","answers":[{"option":"Translocation","bool":false},{"option":"Replication","bool":false},{"option":"Transcription","bool":false},{"option":"Termination","bool":false},{"option":"Translation","bool":true}]},{"id":18,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"An X-linked recessive trait is determined by a gene carried on which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Autosome","bool":false},{"option":"Y-chromosome","bool":false},{"option":"X-chromosome","bool":true},{"option":"Mitochondria","bool":false},{"option":"All the sex chromosomes","bool":false}]},{"id":19,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Anticancer drug etoposide blocks which enzyme in humans?","answers":[{"option":"DNA ligase","bool":false},{"option":"Topoisomerase II","bool":true},{"option":"DNA gyrase","bool":false},{"option":"Topoisomerase I","bool":false},{"option":"DNA swivelase","bool":false}]},{"id":20,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Aphthous stomatitis and erythema nodosum are cutaneous features of which of the following systemic disease?","answers":[{"option":"Diabetes Mellitus","bool":false},{"option":"Crohn's disease","bool":true},{"option":"Typhoid","bool":false},{"option":"Infectious mononucleosis","bool":false},{"option":"Infective endocarditis","bool":false}]},{"id":21,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which is the branch of medicine that deals with helping a person reach their fullest physical, psychological, social, and vocational potentials?","answers":[{"option":"Physiatry","bool":true},{"option":"Speech therapy","bool":false},{"option":"Vocational therapy","bool":false},{"option":"Occupational therapy","bool":false},{"option":"Physiotherapy","bool":false}]},{"id":22,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Cruciform anterior spinal hyperextension (CASH) orthosis is indicated most commonly in which of the following conditions?","answers":[{"option":"Thoracolumbar scoliosis","bool":false},{"option":"Burst fracture of thoracolumbar spine","bool":false},{"option":"Unstable fracture of the thoracic spine","bool":false},{"option":"Ankylosing spondylitis","bool":true},{"option":"Cervical sprain","bool":false}]},{"id":23,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"The blisters that are characteristic of pemphigus are which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Subepidermal acantholytic","bool":false},{"option":"Suprabasal","bool":false},{"option":"Supra basal acantholytic","bool":true},{"option":"Supraclavicular","bool":false},{"option":"Intradermal acantholytic","bool":false}]},{"id":24,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Deletions or point mutations in Ehler Danlos syndrome result in reduced formation of which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Fibrin","bool":false},{"option":"Factors VIII","bool":false},{"option":"Collagen","bool":true},{"option":"Haemoglobin","bool":false},{"option":"Dystrophin","bool":false}]},{"id":25,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Detection of amplified HER2/NEU gene can be done for diagnosis of breast cancer using which of these?","answers":[{"option":"ELISA","bool":false},{"option":"PCR","bool":false},{"option":"FISH","bool":true},{"option":"Southern blotting","bool":false},{"option":"Sequencing","bool":false}]},{"id":26,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following modes of inheritance causes disease when expressed in a homozygous fashion?","answers":[{"option":"Partial expression","bool":false},{"option":"Co-dominance","bool":false},{"option":"Autosomal dominant inheritance","bool":false},{"option":"Double expression","bool":false},{"option":"Autosomal recessive inheritance","bool":true}]},{"id":27,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following is a feature of chickenpox?","answers":[{"option":"Painful eruption all over body","bool":false},{"option":"Oral mucosa is not involved","bool":false},{"option":"Vesicular eruption in a dermatomal pattern","bool":false},{"option":"High grade fever","bool":false},{"option":"Initial lesions are vesicles and papules","bool":true}]},{"id":28,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following is a feature of herpes zoster?","answers":[{"option":"Characterized by intractable itching","bool":false},{"option":"Bilaterally symmetrical lesions","bool":false},{"option":"Mostly affect the mucocutaneous junction","bool":false},{"option":"Caused by reactivation of virus in dorsal root ganglion","bool":true},{"option":"Post herpetic neuralgia is treated by acyclovir","bool":false}]},{"id":29,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following conditions has extensor itchy vesicular eruption along with celiac disease?","answers":[{"option":"Dermatitis herpetiformis","bool":true},{"option":"Pemphigys foliceaous","bool":false},{"option":"Eczema herpeticum","bool":false},{"option":"Herpes gestations","bool":false},{"option":"Herpes zoster","bool":false}]},{"id":30,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following is a mechano-bullous disorder?","answers":[{"option":"Pemphigus","bool":false},{"option":"Epidermolysis bullosa","bool":true},{"option":"Pemphigoid","bool":false},{"option":"Porphyria","bool":false},{"option":"Systemic lupus erythematosus","bool":false}]},{"id":31,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following is the classic clinical presentation of psoriasis?","answers":[{"option":"Lichenification","bool":false},{"option":"Wickham's stria","bool":false},{"option":"Bullous lesion","bool":false},{"option":"Koebner's phenoment","bool":false},{"option":"Plaque with silver white scaling","bool":true}]},{"id":32,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following genes is associated strongly with Gorlin syndrome?","answers":[{"option":"P-53","bool":false},{"option":"KRAS","bool":false},{"option":"PTEN","bool":false},{"option":"P-16","bool":false},{"option":"PTCH1","bool":true}]},{"id":33,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Herbenden nodes are a common feature of which of the following disease processes?","answers":[{"option":"Septic arthritis","bool":false},{"option":"Rheumatoid arthritis","bool":false},{"option":"Reiters syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Osteoarthritis","bool":true},{"option":"Seronegative arthritis","bool":false}]},{"id":34,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Homologous chromosomes can be described as which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Chromosomes similar to parents","bool":false},{"option":"Chromosomes carrying same genes through generations","bool":false},{"option":"Essential chromosomes of diploid cells","bool":false},{"option":"Similar chromosomes with different origin","bool":false},{"option":"Chromosomes of same size and shape","bool":true}]},{"id":35,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Human characters such as height, and intelligence show which inheritance type?","answers":[{"option":"Autosomal","bool":false},{"option":"Single gene","bool":false},{"option":"Mitochondrial","bool":false},{"option":"Polygenic","bool":true},{"option":"X-linked","bool":false}]},{"id":36,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following is a Mendelian disorder?","answers":[{"option":"Phenylketonuria","bool":true},{"option":"Klinefelter syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Cleft lip palate","bool":false},{"option":"Turner syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Down syndrome","bool":false}]},{"id":37,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"If the variation seen in a family is showing autosomal dominant disorders it is due to which of the patterns of inheritance?","answers":[{"option":"Variable expressivity","bool":false},{"option":"Pseudo dominance","bool":false},{"option":"Homozygosity","bool":false},{"option":"Heterozygosity","bool":false},{"option":"Penetrance","bool":true}]},{"id":38,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Difficulty in hearing is defined as which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Dependent hearing","bool":false},{"option":"Handicap","bool":false},{"option":"Disability","bool":false},{"option":"Functional loss","bool":false},{"option":"Impairment","bool":true}]},{"id":39,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"In lateral epicondylitis, which muscle tendon is most prone to getting irritated?","answers":[{"option":"Brachioradialis","bool":false},{"option":"Extensor carpi ulnaris","bool":false},{"option":"Extensor digiti minimi","bool":false},{"option":"Extensor carpi radialis brevis","bool":true},{"option":"Extensor carpi radialis longus","bool":false}]},{"id":40,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which is the most important topical therapy in psoriasis?","answers":[{"option":"Dithranol","bool":false},{"option":"Retinoids","bool":false},{"option":"Calcipotriol","bool":true},{"option":"Emollients/TAR","bool":false},{"option":"Corticosteroids","bool":false}]},{"id":41,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"In rheumatoid arthritis, which of the following is considered to be the most destructive element?","answers":[{"option":"Destruction of synoviocytes","bool":false},{"option":"Infiltration of T lymphocytes","bool":false},{"option":"Cartilage hypertrophy","bool":false},{"option":"Formation of pannus","bool":true},{"option":"B-lymphocyte infiltration","bool":false}]},{"id":42,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following is a common finding in spontaneous abortion?","answers":[{"option":"Diploidy","bool":false},{"option":"Monoploidy","bool":false},{"option":"Octaploidy","bool":false},{"option":"Triploidy","bool":true},{"option":"Polyploidy","bool":false}]},{"id":43,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following is caused by a deficiency of copper that leads to kinky hair and growth retardation?","answers":[{"option":"Wilson disease","bool":false},{"option":"Down syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Maple syrup disease","bool":false},{"option":"Scurvy","bool":false},{"option":"Menkes' syndrome","bool":true}]},{"id":44,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"The malpighian layer contains mitotically active keratinocytes as it is responsible for the turnover of the epidermal keratinocytes. Two layers of epidermis that together are referred to as Malpighian layer include which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Stratum basale and stratum corneum","bool":false},{"option":"Stratum germinativum and stratum spinosum","bool":true},{"option":"Stratum germinativum and stratum granulosum","bool":false},{"option":"Stratum germinativum and stratum corneum","bool":false},{"option":"Stratum basale and stratum lucidum","bool":false}]},{"id":45,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"What is the most appropriate treatment for a child suffering from impetigo?","answers":[{"option":"Oral fluroquinolones","bool":false},{"option":"Topical steroids","bool":false},{"option":"Oral antihistamine","bool":false},{"option":"Oral flucloxacillin and topical antibiotics","bool":true},{"option":"Topical retinoids","bool":false}]},{"id":46,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following is the most common type of tinea pedis?","answers":[{"option":"Dry/hyperkeratotic type of tinea pedis","bool":false},{"option":"Tinea incognito","bool":false},{"option":"Mocassian foot tinea pedia","bool":false},{"option":"Interdigital tinea","bool":true},{"option":"Vesico bullous tinea pedis","bool":false}]},{"id":47,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following is the oral treatment of scabies?","answers":[{"option":"Fluconazole","bool":false},{"option":"5% permethrin","bool":false},{"option":"Acyclovir","bool":false},{"option":"Augmentin","bool":false},{"option":"Ivermectin","bool":true}]},{"id":48,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Phenylketonuria is a genetic disorder due to deficiency of which enzyme?","answers":[{"option":"Thyroxine","bool":false},{"option":"Homogentisic acid","bool":false},{"option":"Tyrosinase","bool":false},{"option":"NADPH oxidase","bool":false},{"option":"Phenyl alanine hydrolase","bool":true}]},{"id":49,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"What is the appropriate approach to physiatry?","answers":[{"option":"Vocational therapist","bool":false},{"option":"Occupational therapist","bool":false},{"option":"Speech therapist","bool":false},{"option":"Multidisciplinary rehabilitation team","bool":true},{"option":"Physiotherapist","bool":false}]},{"id":50,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Pretibial myxedema is a feature of which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Psoriasis","bool":false},{"option":"Internal malignancy","bool":false},{"option":"Hypothyroidism","bool":false},{"option":"Cushing syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Hyperthyroidism","bool":true}]},{"id":51,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Scabies is a communicable disease, which is most commonly noted on?","answers":[{"option":"Axilla","bool":false},{"option":"Elbow","bool":false},{"option":"Groin","bool":false},{"option":"Buttocks","bool":false},{"option":"Webs between fingers","bool":true}]},{"id":52,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Spasticity and clasp knife rigidity is seen in which of the following conditions?","answers":[{"option":"Poliomyelitis syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Lower motor neuron lesion","bool":false},{"option":"Upper motor neuron lesion","bool":true},{"option":"Mitochondrial disease","bool":false},{"option":"Myopathy","bool":false}]},{"id":53,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Spasticity Is defined as which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Increase resistance across a joint range of motion","bool":false},{"option":"Velocity independent decrease in passive stretch of a muscle","bool":false},{"option":"Velocity dependent increase in passive stretch of a muscle","bool":false},{"option":"Velocity dependent increase in resistance during passive stretch of muscle","bool":true},{"option":"Velocity dependent resistance in active stretch of a muscle","bool":false}]},{"id":54,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Target lesions are seen in following type of drug reactions?","answers":[{"option":"Fixed drug eruptions","bool":false},{"option":"Vasculitis","bool":false},{"option":"Steven Johnson's syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Toxic epidermal necrolysis","bool":false},{"option":"Erythrema multiforme","bool":true}]},{"id":55,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following types of disorder are thalassemias classified as?","answers":[{"option":"Y-linked","bool":false},{"option":"X-linked dominant","bool":false},{"option":"X-linked recessive","bool":false},{"option":"Autosomal dominant","bool":false},{"option":"Autosomal recessive","bool":true}]},{"id":56,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following is the best differential diagnosis for tinea corporis?","answers":[{"option":"Lichen planus","bool":false},{"option":"Tuberculoid leprosy","bool":false},{"option":"Bullous impetigo","bool":false},{"option":"Xerotic eczema","bool":false},{"option":"Atopic eczema","bool":true}]},{"id":57,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following is the causative organism of scabies infestation?","answers":[{"option":"Brucella","bool":false},{"option":"Yersinia pestis","bool":false},{"option":"Entamoeba","bool":false},{"option":"Leptospira","bool":false},{"option":"Sarcoptes scabiei","bool":true}]},{"id":58,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"The example of anticipation phenomena is seen in which of the following conditions?","answers":[{"option":"Huntington disease","bool":true},{"option":"Down syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Marfan syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Neurofibromatosis","bool":false},{"option":"Cystic fibrosis","bool":false}]},{"id":59,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following drugs, most widely used in dermatology, causes oligospermia?","answers":[{"option":"Retinoids","bool":false},{"option":"Colchicine","bool":false},{"option":"Methotrexate","bool":true},{"option":"Corticosteroids","bool":false},{"option":"Loratidine","bool":false}]},{"id":60,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following in the germinative zone, exhibits a high rate of growth and is responsible for cell division in nail?","answers":[{"option":"Lunula of nail","bool":false},{"option":"Nail bed","bool":false},{"option":"Nail root","bool":false},{"option":"Nail fold","bool":false},{"option":"Nail matrix","bool":true}]},{"id":61,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"What is the frequency with which allele of a given gene is present in a population is called?","answers":[{"option":"Hardy Weinberg equilibrium","bool":false},{"option":"Allelic diversity","bool":false},{"option":"Gene frequency","bool":false},{"option":"Somatic diversity","bool":false},{"option":"Allele frequency","bool":true}]},{"id":62,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which infection can give rise to erythema multiforme?","answers":[{"option":"Herpes simplex virus","bool":true},{"option":"Scabies","bool":false},{"option":"Pediculosis","bool":false},{"option":"Malaria","bool":false},{"option":"Dermatomyositis","bool":false}]},{"id":63,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of these is the karyotype of Edward's syndrome?","answers":[{"option":"47, XX+ 18","bool":true},{"option":"47, XY +21","bool":false},{"option":"45 XO","bool":false},{"option":"47, XX+13","bool":false},{"option":"47 XXY","bool":false}]},{"id":64,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"What is the loss of one arm of the chromosome with duplication of the other is known as?","answers":[{"option":"Transversion","bool":false},{"option":"Iso chromosome","bool":true},{"option":"Inversion","bool":false},{"option":"Translocation","bool":false},{"option":"Ring chromosome","bool":false}]},{"id":65,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following is the Milwaukee orthosis is categorized as?","answers":[{"option":"Cervicothoracolumbosacral orthosis","bool":true},{"option":"Cervicothoracolumbar orthosis","bool":false},{"option":"Cervicothoracic orthosis","bool":false},{"option":"Lumbosacral orthosis","bool":false},{"option":"Head-Cervical orthosis","bool":false}]},{"id":66,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which is the most common autosomal chromosome syndrome?","answers":[{"option":"Turner syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Klinefelter's syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Marfan syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"XXX syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Down syndrome","bool":true}]},{"id":67,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"What is the most common treatment for scabies?","answers":[{"option":"Sulphur","bool":false},{"option":"Lindane 5%","bool":false},{"option":"Ivermectin","bool":false},{"option":"Permethrin 5%","bool":true},{"option":"Permethrin 1%","bool":false}]},{"id":68,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following is the primary lesion of scabies?","answers":[{"option":"Burrow","bool":true},{"option":"Bulla","bool":false},{"option":"Vesicle","bool":false},{"option":"Crust","bool":false},{"option":"Pustule","bool":false}]},{"id":69,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"The term disturbed health status is used for which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Dependency","bool":false},{"option":"Disability","bool":false},{"option":"Impairment","bool":true},{"option":"Handicap","bool":false},{"option":"Social participation","bool":false}]},{"id":70,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"What is the name for a therapist focusing on exercise and mobilization techniques?","answers":[{"option":"Occupational therapist","bool":false},{"option":"Vocational therapist","bool":false},{"option":"Physical therapist","bool":true},{"option":"Recreational therapist","bool":false},{"option":"Speech therapist","bool":false}]},{"id":71,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following is a therapist who focuses on self-care and functional training of patients?","answers":[{"option":"Occupational therapist","bool":true},{"option":"Vocational therapist","bool":false},{"option":"Physiotherapist","bool":false},{"option":"Social rehabilition therapist","bool":false},{"option":"Physiatrist","bool":false}]},{"id":72,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Using PCR and southern blot we can detect which of the repeats for detection of fragile X syndrome?","answers":[{"option":"ACG","bool":false},{"option":"BCG","bool":false},{"option":"ATG","bool":false},{"option":"TCG","bool":false},{"option":"CGG","bool":true}]},{"id":73,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Vasculitis is a manifestation in which of the following hepatic disorders?","answers":[{"option":"Hepatitis B","bool":true},{"option":"Celiac disease","bool":false},{"option":"Gallbladder carcinoma","bool":false},{"option":"Hepatitis A","bool":false},{"option":"Colon cancer","bool":false}]},{"id":74,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"What is the causative organism of warts?","answers":[{"option":"Herpes simplex I","bool":false},{"option":"Epstein barr virus","bool":false},{"option":"Herpes zoster virus","bool":false},{"option":"Herpes simplex II","bool":false},{"option":"Human papilloma virus","bool":true}]},{"id":75,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"What is the most common clinical diagnostic test for De Quervain's disease?","answers":[{"option":"Phalen test","bool":false},{"option":"Cozen's test","bool":false},{"option":"Durkan test","bool":false},{"option":"Finkelstein test","bool":true},{"option":"Resisted middle finger extension test","bool":false}]},{"id":76,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"When a disease is autosomally inherited, what is the frequency of males and females being affected?","answers":[{"option":"50/50","bool":false},{"option":"100% females","bool":false},{"option":"Equal","bool":true},{"option":"100% males","bool":false},{"option":"25/75","bool":false}]},{"id":77,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"When a segment of one chromosome is inserted into another chromosome, what it is called?","answers":[{"option":"Duplication","bool":false},{"option":"Inversion","bool":false},{"option":"Deletion","bool":false},{"option":"Insertion","bool":true},{"option":"Addition","bool":false}]},{"id":78,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following best describes a freckle?","answers":[{"option":"Decreased pigment","bool":false},{"option":"Macromelanosomes","bool":false},{"option":"Less than 1mm","bool":false},{"option":"Focal abnormality in pigment production by a discrete field of melanocytes","bool":true},{"option":"Increased melanocytes","bool":false}]},{"id":79,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following is the most common lumbar intervertebral disc prolapse?","answers":[{"option":"L1/L2","bool":false},{"option":"L4/L5","bool":false},{"option":"L3/L4","bool":false},{"option":"L5/S1","bool":true},{"option":"L2/L3","bool":false}]},{"id":80,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following systems of classification is used to assess the level of severity in children affected with cerebral palsy?","answers":[{"option":"ASIA","bool":false},{"option":"FAM","bool":false},{"option":"Barthel index","bool":false},{"option":"GMFCS","bool":true},{"option":"FIM","bool":false}]},{"id":81,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following theories is commonly accepted as the mechanism of action of transcutaneous electrical nerve stimulation (TENS)?","answers":[{"option":"Electric theory","bool":false},{"option":"Gate theory","bool":true},{"option":"Chemoelectric theory","bool":false},{"option":"Blast theory","bool":false},{"option":"Desensitization theory","bool":false}]},{"id":82,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which one of the following anti-spasticity agents is least sedative?","answers":[{"option":"Tizanidine","bool":false},{"option":"Midazolam","bool":false},{"option":"Baclofen","bool":false},{"option":"Dantrolene sodium","bool":false},{"option":"Metaxolone","bool":true}]},{"id":83,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which one of the following appliances is given in case of foot drop?","answers":[{"option":"KAFO","bool":false},{"option":"HKFO","bool":false},{"option":"UCBL ORTHOSES","bool":false},{"option":"AFO","bool":true},{"option":"FO","bool":false}]},{"id":84,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which one of the following is a red flag for low back pain due to important pathologies?","answers":[{"option":"Female gender","bool":false},{"option":"Avoidance behavior","bool":false},{"option":"Social isolation","bool":false},{"option":"Back pain in age 20-30 years","bool":false},{"option":"Saddle anaesthesia","bool":true}]},{"id":85,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which one of the following is the most specific test for carpal tunnel syndrome?","answers":[{"option":"Allen's test","bool":false},{"option":"Durkan test","bool":true},{"option":"Cozen's test","bool":false},{"option":"Finkelstein test","bool":false},{"option":"Phalen test","bool":false}]},{"id":86,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which one of the following orthoses is given during the initial months of management of club foot?","answers":[{"option":"Dennis Browne splint","bool":true},{"option":"UCBL orthoses","bool":false},{"option":"Supramalleolar orthosis (SMO)","bool":false},{"option":"AFO","bool":false},{"option":"Rocker bottom shoes","bool":false}]},{"id":87,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which system is rarely affected in erythroderma?","answers":[{"option":"Heart","bool":false},{"option":"Bone","bool":true},{"option":"Skin","bool":false},{"option":"Gastrointestinal","bool":false},{"option":"Kidney","bool":false}]},{"id":88,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Wickham striae are a characteristic feature of which of the following conditions?","answers":[{"option":"Lichen planus","bool":true},{"option":"Candidiasis","bool":false},{"option":"Eczema","bool":false},{"option":"Psoriasis","bool":false},{"option":"Mycosis fungoides","bool":false}]},{"id":89,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"A patient has been diagnosed with carpal tunnel syndrome. What is the newest treatment?","answers":[{"option":"Steriod injection","bool":false},{"option":"Hydrodissection or tranverse carpal ligament release under ultrasound guidance","bool":true},{"option":"Wrist splint","bool":false},{"option":"Low level laser therapy","bool":false},{"option":"Lifestyle modification","bool":false}]},{"id":90,"info":"4th-year/drg/2020","question":"Which of the following is the most frequently asked question by parents of a child affected with cerebral palsy?","answers":[{"option":"Will my child walk?","bool":true},{"option":"Will my child play?","bool":false},{"option":"Will my child communicate?","bool":false},{"option":"Will my child talk?","bool":false},{"option":"Will my child ever be able to study in school?","bool":false}]}]
export default arr